dulcineamedia.com 2009-06-23

# findingDulcinea's Privacy Policy / findingDulcinea

### www.FindingDulcinea.com

FindingDulcinea is published by Dulcinea Media, Inc. ("Dulcinea Media").  We are firmly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all of our users.  To better protect your privacy, this Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by Dulcinea Media. With respect to each aspect of our Web site, we explain what types of information we collect and what we do with it. 

### Newsletters 

Dulcinea Media offers users the option to subscribe to email newsletters that keep subscribers informed about developments on our Web site, such as new features or articles and guides that we publish.  If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we, and our third-party email vendor, will use your name and email address that you voluntarily provide to us to send the newsletter, and that you confirm through a confirmation email request.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a simple and easy way to unsubscribe through a link within our newsletter email.  We and our vendor use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your data used by our system.  We will not share, sell, or rent your individual personal information (including your name or email address) with anyone without your consent or unless required by law.  Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for the purpose of sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. 

### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address) and demographic information (such as zip code).

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose without your consent. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you notice and the choice to opt-out. 

### Tell-A-Friend 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site or an article on our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Dulcinea Media stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We or our third party advertisers use cookies on this Web site to gather certain anonymous information automatically about our users and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  We also use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser.   We do not or combine this anonymous data with any personally identifiable user information. 

You have the ability to accept, decline and delete cookies by modifying your Web browser settings.    However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features of our Web site (and other Web sites) will not be available to you.  For more information on how to change your Web browser settings to disable and/or delete cookies please see the [Interactive Advertising Bureau's "Manage Cookies" article](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/). 

### Web Beacons 

We employ or our third party advertising partner employ Web beacons that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Web beacons are clear gifs (tiny graphics) with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, Web beacons are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.  The Web beacons do not collect any personally identifiable information from our users.  We do not tie the information gathered by Web beacons to our customers' personally identifiable information. 

We use Web beacons in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see "Newsletters". 

### Third Party Advertisers

Dulcinea Media uses trusted and reputable other advertising companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our Web site. Because your web browser must request these advertising banners from the ad network Web site, these companies can send their own cookies to your cookie file.  We only authorize our third-party ad servers to employ anonymous cookies for ad delivery and anonymous targeting. Our third-party ad servers do not collect, nor do we give them access, to any personally identifying information about you.

If you want to opt-out of third party ad network cookies, you may do so through the [Network Advertising Initiative.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Dulcinea Media. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

### Business Transitions

In the event Dulcinea Media goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information voluntarily provided to Dulcinea Media will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via notice on our Web site promptly after any such change in ownership. 

### Changes in this Privacy Statement 

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time.
